A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, Accession 2002:027, SG 2 FA1136
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, Accession 2002:027, SG 2
1993-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund.
FA1136
27.74 Cubic Feet 73 letter document boxes.
Arrangement
As received.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
Primaily consists of grant administration records as well as records created and mantained by the Grants Management Office.
Contains administrative records, budgets, reports, proposals and planning documents, meeting records, program plans and reviews, surveys and briefing books.
Subjects focus primarily on Women's Health including the activities of Commonwealth Fund Commission on Women's Health, the Commonwealth Fund Women's Health Surveys and health care and medicare reform.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund archive was donated to RAC in 1985. Accretions to the collection continue on an ongoing basis. This material was transferred to the Archive Center in 2002.
- Commonwealth Fund Commission on Women's Health, Leiman, Columbia University (96626), 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
- Jacobs Institute of Women's Health (980552), 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 5-9)
- Medicare Reform - Premium Support Proposals, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Medicare Reform - FEHBP, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Medicare Reform - Commonwealth Analysis, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
- Medicare Reform - Commonwealth Analysis, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Medicare Reform - Clinton, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Medicare Reform - Prescription Drug Proposals, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Medicare Reform - Prescription Drug Benefit - Clinton Proposal, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Medicare Reform - Medical Savings Accounts (MSA), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Medicare Reform - Medicare Legislation, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Medicare Reform - Medicare Legislation - Balanced Budget Act of 1997, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Survey of the Health of Adolescent Girls, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Commonwealth Fund Commission on Women's Health Briefing Book, 1995 September 20-21 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Domestic Violence and Women's Health - Broadening the Conversation, 1995 September 20 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- The Health of Adolescent Girls Symposium Briefing Book, 1997 April 15 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Commonwealth Fund Commission on Women's Health, 1993 September 22-23 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- The Health of American Women (924018), 1993 February-March (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Commonwealth Fund Commission on Women's Health Briefing Book, Draft, 1996 September 15 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Women's Health Information Source Book, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Washington Post-Kaiser Family Foundation-Harvard University - Survey of Americans on Gender, 1998 March (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Kaiser Family Foundation - National Survey on Insurance Coverage of Contraceptives, 1998 June (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Cost to Employer Health Plans Covering Contraceptives, J. Darroch, 1998 June (Box 6, Folder 32)
- The Health of U.S. Adolescent Girls, Final Draft, 1998 December (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Changes in Mental Health Care Briefing Book, Atlanta, 1996 October (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Women's Health - Progress and Future, Washington, D.C., 1998 November (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Why Child Care Matters, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Rethinking the Brain, Rima Shore, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- The Many Faces of Domestic Violence - A Curriculum for Community Health Centers, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- The Many Faces of Domestic Violence - A Curriculum for Community Health Centers, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 116)
- Women's Health Files, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 39-43)
- Women's Health Files, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Women's Health Files, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 45-46)
- Evelyn Waltz - Women's Health Survey working papers, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 47-48)
- Karen Davis - Women's Health Files, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 49-50)
- Karen Davis - Women's Health Commission, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Karen Davis - Women's Health Commission, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 52-53)
- Johns Hopkins-Bayview Medical Center (95-017), 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 54-56)
- Medicare Program Files - Medicare Facts, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Medicare Program Files - Medicare Facts, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 58-59)
- Medicare Program Files - Out of Pocket Costs (Box 10, Folder 60-61)
- Medicare Program Files - Prescription Drugs, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 62-63)
- Medicare Program Files - State Pharmaceutical Assistance Program, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 64)
- Medicare Program Files - Prescription Drug Costs, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 65-66)
- Medicare Program Files - Drug Misuse, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 67)
- Medicare Program Files - Direct to Consumer Advertisements, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- Medicare Program Files - Medicare Performance - Fraud and Abuse, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- Medicare Program Files - Medicare Performance - Quality of Care Issues, 1996-2000 (Box 11, Folder 70)
- Medicare Program Files - Medicare Performance - Quality of Care Issues, 1996-2000 (Box 12, Folder 71)
- Medicare Program Files - Medicare Program Performance, 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 72)
- Medicare Program Files - Medicare Financial Issues (Box 12, Folder 73-76)
- Medicare Program Files - Biles, George Washington University - Monitoring Medicare-Plus-Choice Impact, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 77)
- Medicare Program Files - C. Bishop - Medicare NH Reimbursement, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 78)
- Medicare Program Files - Friedland - National Academy on Aging Dual Eligibles, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 79)
- Medicare Program Files - Gold, Mathematica, Medicare-Plus-Choice, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 80-81)
- Medicare Program Files - Howard - Alliance for Health Reform Briefings, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 82)
- Medicare Program Files - Inouye - Delirium Replication, Schelessinger - Evaluation, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 83)
- Medicare Program Files - J. Kasper - Survey of Low Income Elderly in Community, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 84)
- Medicare Program Files - Lewin - LTC Modeling, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 85)
- Medicare Program Files - Moon - Medicare's Future, 1999-2001 (Box 13, Folder 86)
- Medicare Program Files - Murtaugh - New York City Visiting Nurse Service State Home Care Spending, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 87)
- Medicare Program Files - Rutgers, Center for State Health Policy, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 88)
- Medicare Program Files - Safran, New England Medical Center: Survey of Low-Income Elderly, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 89)
- Medicare Program Files - Scheneue, UCLA - Nutrition Intervention, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 90-91)
- Medicare Program Files - Stone - AAHSA - Wellspring, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 92)
- Medicare Program Files - Sofaer - Medicare Choices for New York, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 93)
- Medicare Program Files - Tilly-Weiner - Urban Consumer-Directed Home Care, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 94)
- Medicare Program Files - Limmerman - Quality Indicators, 1999-2001 (Box 14, Folder 95)
- Medicare Program Files - Nursing Home and Aging Care (Box 14, Folder 96-97)
- Medicare Program Files - Program Monitoring Committee, 2000 June (Box 14, Folder 98)
- Medicare Program Files - Dual Eligibles Partnership, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 99)
- Medicare Program Files - Committee on Care at the End of Life, 1996 June 6-7 (Box 15, Folder 100-101)
- Medicare Program Files - Committee on Care at the End of Life, 1996 August 29-30 (Box 15, Folder 102)
- Medicare Program Files - Grantmakers Concerned with End of Life Care, 1997 June 12 (Box 15, Folder 103)
- Victims Services Domestic Violence Prevention (96527), 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 104-105)
- Victims Services Domestic Violence Prevention (96527), 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 106-107)
- Victims Services - HMO Advisory Board Meeting, 1995 November (Box 16, Folder 108-109)
- Girl's Health - Adolescent Attitudes Toward and Access to Health Care Report, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 110)
- Louis Harris and Associates - In the News, 1998 January-April (Box 16, Folder 111)
- Women's Health Survey II - Banner Books, 1998 December-1999 January (Box 17, Folder 112-113)
- Reproductive Health and New York's Changing Health Care System, 1998 June 5 (Box 17, Folder 114)
- National Summit on Women's Health and Managed Care, Washington, D.C., 1999 March 10-11 (Box 17, Folder 115)
- Hospital Youth Mentoring Program - Final Report (Johns Hopkins), 1994-995 (Box 17, Folder 117)
- Hospital Youth Mentoring Program - Final Report (Johns Hopkins), 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 118)
- Domestic Violence Report, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 119)
- American Association of Health Plans (AAHP) Monographs, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 120)
- American Association of Health Plans (AAHP) Midlife Report, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 121)
- American Association of Health Plans (AAHP) Women's Health Activities, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 122-123)
- MDS Authors, Survey, Comments, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 124)
- Women's Health Survey 1997 - Instrument Development (Box 19, Folder 125)
- Women's Health Survey 1997 (Box 19, Folder 126-127)
- Women's Health Survey, 1996 July (Box 19, Folder 128)
- Women's Health Survey 1998, 1997-1999 (Box 19, Folder 129)
- Women's Health Survey 1998, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 130-135)
- Women's Health Survey 1998, 1997-1999 (Box 21, Folder 136)
- Women's Health Survey II - Banner Books, 1998 September 30 (Box 21, Folder 137-139)
- Women's Health Survey II - Banner Books, 1998 September 30 (Box 22, Folder 140-144)
- Women's Health Survey II - Banner Books, 1998 September 30 (Box 23, Folder 145)
- Women's Health Survey II - Banner Books, 1998 December (Box 23, Folder 146-148)
- Women's Health Survey II - Banner Books, 1998 December (Box 24, Folder 149-152)
- Women's Health Survey II - Banner Books, 1998 December (Box 25, Folder 153-155)
- Women's Health Survey II - Banner Books, 1999 January (Box 25, Folder 156-157)
- Women's Health Survey II - Banner Books, 1999 January (Box 26, Folder 158-162)
- Women's Health Survey I - Adolescent Girls Health (Box 27, Folder 163)
- Women's Health Survey II - The 1998 Health of American Women Survey - Drafts, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 164-165)
- Women's Health Tabulations - 2nd Revised Version, Volume 3 (Box 27, Folder 166)
- AAHP - Improving Health Services for Women Enrolled in Managed Care Plans, 1998 September (Box 28, Folder 167-168)
- Commonwealth Fund Commission on Women's Health - Briefing Books, 1994-1996 (Box 28, Folder 169-172)
- Commonwealth Fund Commission on Women's Health - Briefing Books, 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 173-174)
- American Association of Health Plans (AAHP) - Bocchino (970277), 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 175-177)
- University of Connecticut - Flitcraft (970236) - Domestic Violence Initiative in Community Health Centers, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 178)
- University of Connecticut - Flitcraft (970236) - Domestic Violence Initiative in Community Health Centers, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 179-180)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Taylor (96956) - Women's Health Survey 1997, 1996-1999 (Box 30, Folder 181)
- MDS Associates - Falik (96954) - Symposia and Policy Reports on Women's Health, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 182-184)
- Victim Services - Friedman (96527) - Domestic Violence Intervention Project, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 185)
- Victim Services - Friedman (96527) - Domestic Violence Intervention Project, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 186-187)
- Domestic Violence Symposium, 1995-1997 (Box 31, Folder 188-191)
- Hospital Youth Mentoring Program - Final Report (Johns Hopkins) (96005), 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 192-194)
- Hospital Youth Mentoring Program - Midyear Report (Johns Hopkins) (96844), 1996 August-1997 January (Box 32, Folder 195-196)
- Hospital Youth Mentoring Program - Final Report (Johns Hopkins), 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 197)
- Study of Women's Health Centers - Final Report (Johns Hopkins) (94-54), 1995 December 31 (Box 33, Folder 198)
- Women's Health Campaign - Summary, 1997 February 1-4 (Box 33, Folder 199)
- National Survey of Adults Mentoring Young People, 1998 April 7 (Box 33, Folder 200)
- Nursing Home - Residential Alternatives, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 201)
- Nursing Home Alternatives, 1995-1999 (Box 34, Folder 202-203)
- Housing for Elderly, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 204)
- Nursing Homes, 1995-2000 (Box 35, Folder 205-206)
- Nursing Home Quality, 1998-2000 (Box 35, Folder 207-209)
- Nursing Home Quality, 1998-2000 (Box 36, Folder 210-212)
- End of Life Care, 1995-2000 (Box 36, Folder 213)
- End of Life Care, 1995-2000 (Box 37, Folder 214)
- Long-Term Care in New York - Issue Brief, 1998-1999 (Box 37, Folder 215-216)
- Long-Term Care files, 1998-2000 (Box 37, Folder 217-218)
- Long-Term Care Insurance, 1996-2000 (Box 37, Folder 219)
- Long-Term Care Insurance, 1996-2000 (Box 38, Folder 220)
- Long-Term Care Reform, 1996-1999 (Box 38, Folder 221)
- Medicaid Program, 1995-2000 (Box 38, Folder 222-224)
- Medicaid Program, 1995-2000 (Box 39, Folder 225-227)
- Home Health Care (Box 39, Folder 229-231)
- Home Health Care (Box 40, Folder 232)
- Medicare Home Health Benefit, 1998-2000 (Box 40, Folder 233)
- Current Grants - Active - Moon, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 234)
- Current Grants - Active - Gold, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 235)
- Current Grants - Active - Stuart, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 236)
- Friedland on QMB-SLMB Outreach, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 237)
- Rice - Medigap Switchers, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 238)
- Liberman Consumer Book, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 239)
- Mollica - Nursing Home Survey, Enforcement, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 240)
- Zimmerman - Quality Indicators, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 241)
- Wellspring Planning - AAHSA, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 242)
- Murtaugh - State Home Care Spending, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 243)
- Bishop - Nursing Home Access, Quality, 1998-2000 (Box 41, Folder 244)
- Korbin Liu - Medical Capitation, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 245)
- Elderly Program Reviews, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 246)
- Long-Term Care Program Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 247)
- Long-Term Care Program Plan, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 248)
- Long-Term Care Program Plan, 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 249)
- Frail Elders Program Planning, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 250)
- Frail Elders Program Planning, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 251)
- Medicare Program Planning, 1998-1999 (Box 42, Folder 252)
- Medicare Program Planning, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 253-254)
- Board Meetings - Elderly Advisory Committee, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 255)
- Board Meetings - Program Monitoring Committee, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 256)
- Board Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 42, Folder 257)
- Medicare Managed Care, 1996-2000 (Box 42, Folder 258-259)
- Medicare Managed Care, 1996-2000 (Box 43, Folder 260-261)
- Medicare-Plus-Choice, 1996-2000 (Box 43, Folder 262-264)
- Medicare-Plus-Choice, 1996-2000 (Box 44, Folder 265-269)
- Medicare Reform - Commission Recommendations, 1998-2000 (Box 45, Folder 270-272)
- Commonwealth Fund Commission on Women's Health Briefing Book, 1996 April 10-11 (Box 45, Folder 273)
- Commonwealth Fund Commission on Women's Health Briefing Book, 1996 October 2-3 (Box 45, Folder 274)
- Commonwealth Fund Commission on Women's Health Briefing Book, 1997 September 24-25 (Box 45, Folder 275)
- Women's Health Program Review, 1996 January 26 (Box 45, Folder 276)
- Shalala - Briefing Book (Box 46, Folder 277)
- Women's Health Survey I - Adolescent Health Study, Final Weighted Tabulations - Banners 2-7, 1997 July 3 (Box 46, Folder 278-280)
- HEDIS 3.0, Volumes I and 2 (Box 47, Folder 281)
- Women's Health Measurement Advisory Panel (MAP) - CVs, 1996-1997 (Box 47, Folder 282)
- Women's Health Measurement Advisory Panel (MAP) - Selected Women's Health Measures (Box 47, Folder 283)
- Women's Health Measurement Advisory Panel (MAP) - Background Reading for Clinical Assessment of Women's Health Discussion, 1996-1997 (Box 47, Folder 284)
- Women's Health Files, 1993-2000 (Box 48, Folder 285-288)
- Mental Health Files, 1997-2000 (Box 49, Folder 286)
- Rural Health Files, 1995-1997 (Box 49, Folder 287)
- General Health Care Reform Files, 1993-2000 (Box 49, Folder 288-290)
- Clinton Health Care Reform, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 291)
- Social Security Reform (Box 49, Folder 292)
- Social Security Reform (Box 50, Folder 293)
- Medicare Reform Public Opinion, 1998-2000 (Box 50, Folder 294-295)
- Focus on the Family, 1996-1998 (Box 50, Folder 296-297)
- Commonwealth Fund Commission on Women's Health Briefing Book, 1997 April 15-16 (Box 50, Folder 298)
- Meeting the Health Care Needs of Women - Developing an Agenda (A Resource Guide), 1992 (Box 51, Folder 299-300)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) - Meeting of the Women's Health Advisory Panel, 1997 July 24-25 (Box 51, Folder 301-302)
- The Health of Adolescent Girls Symposium Briefing Book, 1997 April 15 (Box 51, Folder 303)
- Preventive Health Services for Women - Research and Resource Kit (Box 51, Folder 304)
- French-American Foundation Report, 1996 September (Box 52, Folder 305)
- American Association of Health Plans (AAHP) - Advancing Women's Health, 1998 June (Box 52, Folder 306)
- Women's Health Survey 1998 - Preliminary Analysis, 1998 November (Box 52, Folder 307)
- Women's Health Survey 1998 - Banner Plans (Box 52, Folder 308)
- Women's Health Survey 1998 - Background Articles and Output, 1998-1999 (Box 52, Folder 309)
- Women's Health Survey 1998 - Background Articles and Output, 1998-1999 (Box 53, Folder 310)
- Jacobs Institute of Women's Health - Romans (990908) - Preventive Care and Patient Counseling (Box 53, Folder 311-312)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) (970651) - Development of Quality Performance Measures (Box 53, Folder 313-315)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance (NCQA) (970651) - Development of Quality Performance Measures (Box 54, Folder 316-319)
- Domestic Violence - Friedman (96527), 1996-1999 (Box 54, Folder 320)
- Domestic Violence - Friedman (96527), 1996-1999 (Box 55, Folder 321)
- Emory University - Nordenberg (980842) - Child Abuse and Family Violence, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 322-323)
- Women's Health Files, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 324)
- Brandeis University-GIH (980772) - Health Issue Forums with Local Foundations (Box 55, Folder 325-326)
- Mental Health Symposium, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 327)
- Adolescent Health Symposium, 1996-1997 (Box 56, Folder 328)
- Louis Harris and Associates (95-09) - Low Income Managed Care Study (Box 56, Folder 329-332)
- AAHP Domestic Violence Consumer Booklet, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 333)
- AAHP Hormone Replacement-Midlife Consumer Booklet, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 334)
- AAHP Breast Cancer Report, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 335)
- Survey of the Quality of Midlife, 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 336)
- Women's Health Measurement Advisory Panel (MAP), 1998 (Box 57, Folder 337)
- Women's Health Commission - Domestic Violence - Background papers, 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 338-340)
- Women's Health Commission - Health Care Access and Coverage for Women Report, 1993-1999 (Box 58, Folder 341-343)
- OTT, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 344)
- SJ Correspondence, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 345)
- Women's Program - Presidential Discretionary Fund (PDF)- Mullen, 1995-1996 (Box 58, Folder 346)
- Women's Program - Presidential Discretionary Fund (PDF) - Schaps, 1996-1997 (Box 58, Folder 347)
- Women's Program - Presidential Discretionary Fund (PDF) - Glied, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 348)
- Women's Program - Presidential Discretionary Fund (PDF) - Robinson, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 349)
- Women's Program - Presidential Discretionary Fund (PDF) - Klein, 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 350)
- Women's Program - Presidential Discretionary Fund (PDF) - Education Development Center, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 351)
- University of Michigan - Saunders (980413) - Relationship Between Domestic Abuse, Poverty and Women's Health, 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 352)
- UCLA - Wenzel (980599) - Violence Against Homeless Women, 1998-1999 (Box 59, Folder 353-354)
- FACCT, Inc. - Bethel (980495) - Measuring the Quality of Adolescent Preventive Health Care Services, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 355-357)
- Louis Harris Associates - Binns (980667) - Men's Health Expansion of the 1998 Survey of Women's Health, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 358)
- Louis Harris Associates - Binns (990532) - Reweighing the 1993 Survey of Women's Health, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 359)
- NYU - Blustein (20000099) - Vulnerability to Out-of-Pocket Costs Under Medicare, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 360)
- Adolescent Health Book, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 361)
- Casey Foundation Speech, 1998 July (Box 60, Folder 362)
- Improving Health Care Services Program - Active Grants, 1997 June (Box 60, Folder 363)
- Casey Journalism Fellows Symposium, 1998 June (Box 60, Folder 364)
- Jacobs Institute, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 365)
- Foundations - Grantmakers, 1999-2000 (Box 60, Folder 366-367)
- Aging Organizations, 1998-2000 (Box 61, Folder 368-370)
- End of Life Care Organizations, 1997-2000 (Box 61, Folder 371)
- End of Life Care Organizations, 1997-2000 (Box 62, Folder 372)
- Grantmakers in Health, 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 373)
- Grantmakers in Aging, 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 374-375)
- Major National Meetings - GSA, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 376)
- Major National Meetings - AHSR, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 377)
- Commonwealth Fund Sponsored Events, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 378)
- Database Information - Background, 1996-1999 (Box 63, Folder 379)
- Database Information - Medicare Current Beneficiary Survey (MCBS), 1999 (Box 63, Folder 380)
- Database Information - Minimum Data Set (MDS)-Resident Assessment Investment (RAI), 1995-1998 (Box 63, Folder 381)
- Database Information - OSCAR (Box 63, Folder 382)
- Database Information - OASIS, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 383)
- Database Information - Medical Expenditure Panel Survey (MEPS), 1997-1999 (Box 63, Folder 384)
- Presidential Discretionary Fund (PDF) - Kay Johnson - Home Visiting, 1998 July (Box 63, Folder 385)
- Presidential Discretionary Fund (PDF) - Children Now, 1997-1998 (Box 63, Folder 386)
- National Advisory Committee Meetings, 1996-2000 (Box 63, Folder 387-388)
- National Advisory Committee Meetings, 1996-2000 (Box 64, Folder 389-395)
- National Advisory Committee Meetings, 1996-2000 (Box 65, Folder 396-401)
- National Advisory Committee Meetings, 1996-2000 (Box 66, Folder 402)
- Access to Health Care in New York City - Urban Poor Statistics (Box 66, Folder 403)
- Independent Production Fund (IPF) (990470) - Phase III, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 404)
- Zero to Three, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 405)
- Conference Call Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 66, Folder 406)
- Healthy Steps - Multimedia Project, 1998-1999 (Box 66, Folder 407-409)
- University of Connecticut - Flitcraft (95446) - Domestic Violence Initiative in Community Health Centers - Phase II, 1994-1996 (Box 67, Folder 410-415)
- Mt. Sinai - Plichta (95-41) - Model Projects for Battered Women, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 416-418)
- Mt. Sinai - Plichta (95-41) - Model Projects for Battered Women, 1994-1997 (Box 70, Folder 430-432)
- Columbia University - Leiman (96953) - Commission on Women's Health - Symposia and Policy Reports, 1996-1998 (Box 68, Folder 419-421)
- Columbia University - Leiman (980207) - Commission on Women's Health - Symposia and Policy Reports - Phase II, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 422-425)
- Covance (990203) - Development of Quality Performance Measures for Women's Health, 1998-1999 (Box 69, Folder 426-427)
- Covance (990203) - Development of Quality Performance Measures for Women's Health, 1998-2000 (Box 70, Folder 428-429)
- Improving the Health of Adolescent Girls (Adolescent Policy Report), 1996-1999 (Box 71, Folder 433-437)
- Adolescent Chart Book, 1998-1999 (Box 72, Folder 438-440)
- National Asian Women's Health Organization (NAWHO), 1998-1999 (Box 72, Folder 441-442)
- Reproductive Health, 1996-1999 (Box 73, Folder 443)
- Adolescent Health Materials, 1997-1999 (Box 73, Folder 444)
- Women's Program Overview, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 445-446)
- Woods Drafts, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 447-448)
- Magazine Briefing - Editor's Lunch, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 449)